Guide to the Dept. of Music Sound Recordings, 1956 - 1990 UA.25.28.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Dept. of Music sound recordings
1956 - 1990
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Duke University. Department of Music
UA.25.28.0001
51 Linear Feet
In 1942, Duke University created the Department of Aesthetics, Art and Music. In 1960, the Department of Music formed as a separate department. Allan H. Bone, Duke professor from 1940 to 1983 and conductor of the Duke Symphony, was instrumental in the formation of the department. British composer Iain Hamilton was a faculty member for seventeen years. The Dept. of Music Sound Recordings collection contains audiotapes made between 1956 and 1990, primarily on 1/4 inch reel to reel tape, of the Duke Symphony Orchestra, the Duke Wind Symphony, the Duke Glee Club, the Ciompi Quartet, and the Duke Collegium Musicum, as well as other recordings related to the faculty and students of the Duke University Department of Music. There are also audiocassettes and a few videotapes. Faculty members represented include Jane Hawkins, Penelope Jensen, Randall Love, Robert Parkins, Fred Raimi, Claudia Warburg, and Ruth Friedburg. Other featured musicians are Milton Babbitt, Barbara Lister-Sink, Claudia Bloom, Boaz Sharon, and Bruce Berg. English.
680 Items
Access Restrictions
Patrons must sign the Acknowledgement of Legal Responsibility and Privacy Rights form before using this collection.
In off-site storage; 24 hours advance notice is required for use.
Use of this collection requires the creation of listening copies from audiotapes or viewing copies from videotapes. However, University Archives does not have the equipment or the resources to make copies from reel-to-reel tape, U-Matic videocassettes, Betamax videocassettes, or open reel video. To arrange for the creation of use copies from these formats, please contact University Archives staff. Although these recordings are now stored in a stable environment, their condition and playback quality is unknown.
Provenance
The Dept. of Music Sound Recordings was received by the University Archives as a transfer in 2005.
Historical Note
In 1942, Duke University created the Department of Aesthetics, Art and Music. In 1960, the Department of Music formed as a separate department. Allan H. Bone, Duke professor from 1940 to 1983 and conductor of the Duke Symphony, was instrumental in the formation of the department. British composer Iain Hamilton was a faculty member for seventeen years.
Collection Overview
The Dept. of Music Sound Recordings collection contains audiotapes made between 1956 and 1990, primarily on 1/4 inch reel to reel tape, of the Duke Symphony Orchestra, the Duke Wind Symphony, the Duke Glee Club, the Ciompi Quartet, and the Duke Collegium Musicum, as well as other recordings related to the faculty and students of the Duke University Department of Music. There are also audiocassettes and a few videotapes. Faculty members represented include Jane Hawkins, Penelope Jensen, Randall Love, Robert Parkins, Fred Raimi, Claudia Warburg, and Ruth Friedburg. Other featured musicians are Milton Babbitt, Barbara Lister-Sink, Claudia Bloom, Boaz Sharon, and Bruce Berg.
Separated Material
Robert Hill, 1986:
1 sound reel; 12-inch, 1/4 inch
Stored in the University Archives audio collection, Box D4.
Related Material
Allan H. Bone Papers, 1944-1989
Duke University Archives
Sound recordings; Duke University. Department of Music; Duke University. Department of Music; Duke University. Symphony Orchestra; Duke University. Glee Club; Duke University -- Faculty; Duke Collegium Musicum; Duke University. Chapel Choir; Duke University Wind Symphony; Bloom, Claudia; Berg, Bruce, violinist; Ciompi Quartet; Bone, Allan H.; Babbitt, Milton, 1916-; Sharon, Boaz; Lister-Sink, Barbara; Love, Randall; Parkins, Robert; Raimi, Fred; Friedberg, Ruth C., 1928-; Hamilton, Iain, 1922-; Hawkins, Jane; Jensen, Penelope
- Accession UA2005-0060
  - Men's Glee Club Concerts, 1958-1969, 36 sound reels; 7-inch, 1/4 inch. (Box 1)
  - Men's and Women's Glee Club, Chancel Singers, Chapel Choir, Madrigal Singers, 1958-1971, 37 sound reels; 7-inch, 1/4 inch. (Box 2)
  - Chorale, 1970-1980, 29 sound reels; 7-inch, 1/4 inch, 9 sound cassettes. (Box 3)
  - Chorale, 1980-1987, 12 sound reels; 10-inch, 1/4 inch. (Box 4)
  - Chorale, 1987, 4 sound reels; 10-inch, 1/4 inch. (Box 5)
  - Miscellaneous recordings, 18 sound reels; 7-inch, 1/4 inch, 5 sound reels; 5-inch, 1/4 inch. (Box 5)
  - Wind Symphony, NC Symphony, Duke Symphony Orchestra, 1975-1986, 26 sound reels; 7-inch, 1/4 inch. (Box 6)
  - Guest Artist--Ernest White: Music for Organ and Strings, 1962, 4 sound reels; 7-inch, 1/4 inch. (Box 6)
  - Flentrop Organ Dedication, 1976, 3 sound reels; 7-inch, 1/4 inch. (Box 6)
  - Organ Symposium, 1976, 2 sound reels; 7-inch, 1/4 inch. (Box 6)
  - Flentrop Organ, Duke Chapel, 1978, 1 sound reel; 7-inch, 1/4 inch. (Box 6)
  - Collegium Musicum, 1974-1990, 24 sound reels; 7-inch, 1/4 inch. (Box 7)
  - Robert Parkins, 1979-1980, 7 sound reels; 7-inch, 1/4 inch. (Box 7)
  - Duke Wind Symphony, 1990, 2 sound reels; 7-inch, 1/4 inch. (Box 7)
  - Ciompi Quartet, 1991, 1 sound reel; 7-inch, 1/4 inch. (Box 7)
  - Organ Recital, 1991, 1 sound reel; 7-inch, 1/4 inch. (Box 7)
  - Largo, Maryland, 1969, 1 sound reel; 7-inch, 1/4 inch. (Box 7)
  - DSO Bone and Kitchen, 1981, 2 sound reels; 10-inch, 1/4 inch. (Box 8)
  - Jonathan Bag Demo, 1990 and undated, 4 sound reels; 10-inch, 1/4 inch. (Box 8)
  - DSO Bone and Kitchen, 1981, 2 sound reels; 7-inch, 1/4 inch. (Box 8)
  - Allan Bone, undated, 4 sound reels; 7-inch, 1/4 inch. (Box 8)
  - Composers Forum, undated, 1 sound reel; 7-inch, 1/4 inch. (Box 8)
  - Organ Recital, 1990, 1 sound reel; 7-inch, 1/4 inch. (Box 8)
  - Tibor Szasz, 1990, 3 sound reels; 7-inch, 1/4 inch. (Box 8)
  - Patricia Applegate recital, Alumni Commons Room, October 16, 1973, 2 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 9)
  - Thornton and Wuensch recital, April 21, 1972, 3 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 9)
  - Sarah Wendt and Louis Auld recital, Duke University Art Museum, January 30, 1972, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 9)
  - Hanks students recital with Patricia Applegate, Steve Watson, and Sarah Wendt, undated, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 9)
  - Opera Workshop, Figaro, undated, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 9)
  - Music from Duke: A Composer's Forum, Asbury Recital Hall, March 27, 1973, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 9)
  - Composers, undated, 2 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 9)
  - Iain Hamilton, The Royal Hunt of the Sun, Introduction to BBC Broadcast, October 17, 1964, 1 sound reel, 5-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 9)
    Arrangement note
    [Use copy available.]
  - Lukas Foss-Iain Hamilton interview on WUNC-TV, 1964-1965, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 9)
  - Milton Babbit-Iain Hamilton performance interview, February 19, 1965, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 9)
  - Iain Hamilton, Talk on Hamilton Works, East Campus Library, October 17, 1964, 2 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 9)
  - An Evening with Iain Hamilton, New Dimensions in Music, October 13, 1964, 1 sound reel, 5-inch, 1/4 inch; 3 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 9)
  - Karen Van Kannon recital, April 29, 1973, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 9)
  - Carol Jaffee recital, March 31, 1973, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 9)
  - Lawrence Bassman, Hoffmeister Quintet, [c. 1972], 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 9)
  - Fowley's Lignes de Sonde, undated, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 9)
  - Saville, Mozart's Horn Concerto No. 3, January 9, 1971, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 9)
  - Mac Phillips recital, undated, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 9)
  - Karen Van Kannon, Patricia Wuensch recitals, December 2, 1972, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 9)
  - A Program in Celebration of Jewish Music Month, March 27, 1973, 2 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 9)
  - Charles Register senior recital, December 11, 1972, 2 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 9)
  - Nanette Bishopric Senior Recital, April 13, 1973, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 9)
  - Melville Brown Junior Recital, April 21, 1973, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 9)
  - Student Recitals, 1964-1977 and undated, 9 sound reels; 7-inch, 1/4 inch, 2 sound reels; 5-inch, 1/4 inch. (Box 10)
    - Maurice Wright, Study 1 No. 2 Reading, August 24, 1970, 1 sound reel, 5-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 10)
    - Maurice Wright, Three Pieces concert, August 19, 1970, 1 sound reel, 5-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 10)
    - Sarah Wendt Recital, April 18, 1972, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 10)
    - Ken Shifrin Recital, March 1972, 2 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 10)
    - Larry Sherr Recital, February 21, 1977, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 10)
    - Student Recital, March 8, 1964, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 10)
    - [Litzie], undated, 2 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 10)
    - Bishopric and Brown recital, April 21, 1972, 2 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 10)
  - Student Chamber Ensembles, March 30, 1989, 1 videocassette (Betamax (Box 10)
  - Duke Collegium Musicum, November 23, 1986, 2 sound reels; 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 10)
  - Music Department Faculty Retreat, September 1978, 4 sound reels; 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 10)
  - Biddle Building Dedication, 1974, 19 sound reels; 7-inch, 1/4 inch
    - Duke Symphony Orchestra, October 17, 1974, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 10)
    - Panel Discussion on The Economics of Music and Music Education, October 18, 1974, 2 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 10)
    - North Carolina Symphony Quintet, Robert Schuman Lecture, October 18, 1974, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 10)
    - Chapel Performance, October 19, 1974, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 10)
    - Panel Discussion on Music Criticism, October 19, 1974, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 10)
    - Ciompi Quartet with Julia Mueller, October 19, 1974, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 10)
    - Duke Jazz Ensemble, October 19, 1974, 2 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 10)
    - Music Building Dedication, October 19, 1974, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 10)
    - Organ lecture and Collegium Musicum, October 20, 1974, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 10)
    - Dedication Ceremonies, Duke Chapel, October 20, 1974, 2 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 10)
    - Dizzy Gillespie, undated, 2 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 10)
    - [Veena-Baldwin Recital], undated, 2 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 10)
  - Duke Symphony Orchestra and Duke Jazz Ensemble, December 10, 1975, 4 sound reels; 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 11)
  - Doc Dikeman, Page Auditorium, September 15, 1979, 3 sound reels; 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 11)
  - Ted Dikeman and Orchestra at Willowmill Recorders, August 29, 1978, 1 sound reel; 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 11)
  - A Lecture-Recital of Songs by John Duke, November 5, 1963, 2 sound reels; 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 11)
  - Guitar Slim performing for jazz history class, 1977, 1 sound reel; 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 11)
  - Miscellaneous recordings, 6 sound reels; 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 11)
  - Big Band Bash, WUNC-TV, March 18, 1978, 3 videocassettes (U-matic) (Box 11)
  - A Bit of Jazz [Possibly Biddle Building dedication], undated, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch. (Box 12)
  - Brother Yusef, I Remember Mary Lou, Children's Jazz Show, April 15, 1983, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch. (Box 12)
  - Encounters concert with soprano Victoria Villamil, November 18, 1982, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 12)
  - Lost Eden: A Chancel Opera in Two Acts, November 7-8, 1982, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 12)
  - Encounters concert, The Music of Arnold Schoenberg, February 27, 1983, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 12)
  - Ciompi Quartet Winterfest concert, January 18, 1985, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 12)
  - A Mendelssohn-Schumann Concert, in Conjunction with the International Mendelssohn-Schumann Conference, April 2, 1982, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 12)
  - Encounters concert with composer John Newell, March 19, 1985, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 12)
  - Student Composers' Concert, April 15, 1985, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 12)
    Scope and Contents note
    Includes Anthony Kelley, Essay for Piano in E-flat minor.
  - Music and Dance from West Java, Pak Katiyo, dir., February 24, 1985, 1 sound reel; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 12)
    Part of the Indian Ocean Arts Festival’s inauguration of the gamelan instruments
  - Indonesian Puppet Performance, March 30, 1985, 2 sound reels; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 12)
  - Student Composers' Concert, April 15, 1982, 2 sound reels; 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 12)
  - Student Composers' Concert, April 21, 1983, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 12)
  - The Last Straw, undated, 1 sound reel; 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 12)
  - Michael Ching-Levee's opera, undated, 1 sound reel; 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 12)
  - Five Evenings with Iain Hamilton, 1963, 16 sound reels; 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 13)
    - Luigi Dallapiccola Concert, November 18, 1962, 2 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 13)
    - Stravinsky Concert, November 18, 1963, 5 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 13)
    - Seminar: The Contemporary Arts: Common Denominators, April 15, 1963, 3 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 13)
      [Use copy available].
    - Seminar: Great Non-Radicals, Including Messiaen and Shostakovich, October 11, 1963, 6 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 13)
    - Iain Hamilton Seminars: Music Now and Background to 20th Century Music, March 9, 1962, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 13)
    - Iain Hamilton Lecture: The Composer and Opera, March 19, 1968, 3 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 13)
  - Third Music Educators Conference, February 22, 1964, 12 sound reels; 7-inch, 1/4 inch
    - New York Brass Quintet, 3 sound reels; 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 13)
    - New York Woodwind Quintet, 1964, 6 sound reels; 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 13)
  - Music for Organ and Strings, featuring Ernest White, January 7, 1962, 1 sound reel; 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 13)
  - Chamber Concert Rehearsal, February 1958, 2 sound reels; 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 13)
  - Unlabeled, undated, 1 sound reel; 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 13)
  - Milton Babbitt, Electronic Music, undated, 2 sound reels; 10-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 14)
  - Iain Hamilton, Lukas Foss, Ronald Hodges, Hindemuth, 1965 and undated, 13 sound reels; 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 14)
  - Music 186-A, undated, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 14)
  - Five Evenings with Iain Hamilton, 1964-1965 and undated, 11 sound reels; 7-inch, 1/4 inch
    - A Benjamin Britten Evening, March 24, 1964, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 14)
    - Lukas Foss Concert, February 11, 1965, 4 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 14)
    - Fourth Evening with Iain Hamilton, undated, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 14)
    - Milton Babbitt lecture, February 19, 1965, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 14)
    - Miscellaneous, 1964-1965, 4 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 14)
  - Klenz Music 138 lecture on Hindemith, undated, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 14)
  - Duke Symphony Orchestra, 1958-1965 and undated, 14 sound reels; 7-inch, 1/4 inch
    - April 22, 1960 concert, 2 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 14)
    - 1959-1960 season, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 14)
    - November 20, 1962 concert, 3 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 14)
    - November 17, 1964 concert, 2 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 14)
    - March 18, 1965 concert (Handel-Harty and Hamilton), 2 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 14)
    - April 1958 concert featuring Earl Slocum, 2 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 14)
    - November 18, 1960 concert featuring Joseph Pepper, 2 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 14)
  - Duke University Concert Band, Flag of Stars, March 24, 1960, 1 sound reel; 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 14)
  - Duke University Concert Band, April 13, 1960, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 14)
  - Ronald Hodges Piano Recital, March 23, 1965, 2 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 14)
  - Recital with Julia Mueller and Ruth Friedberg, October 23, 1962, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 14)
  - John Hanks concert, February 26, 1962, 2 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 14)
  - Faculty Chamber Music Program, February 6, 1962, 2 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 14)
  - Men's Glee Club, 1956-1967, 9 sound reels; 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 15)
    - 1956-1957 season, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 15)
    - Northern Tour, March 30, 1967, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 15)
    - Philadelphia, 1963, 4 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 15)
    - Dad's Day Concert, October 31, 1958, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 15)
    - Graduation Concert, June 2, 1956, 2 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 15)
  - Raphael Hillyer Recital, January 16, 1976, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 15)
  - Chancel Singers, February 5, 1965, 2 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 15)
  - Spring Concert, April 23, 1965, 3 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 15)
  - Duke Symphony Orchestra, 1962-1964, 11 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch
    - March 12, 1964 concert, 6 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 15)
    - December 17, 1963 concert, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 15)
    - November 20, 1962 concert, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 15)
    - March 20, 1963 concert with Anthony di Bonaventura, 2 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 15)
    - November 17, 1964 concert with Giorgio Ciompi, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 15)
  - Unlabeled, undated, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 15)
  - Duke University String Quartet, Live WPTF Performance, November 1965, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 15)
  - North Carolina Symphony and Woodwind Quintet, May 4, 1974, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 15)
  - Duke and UNC Symphonies, October 24, 1990, 2 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 15)
  - Student Chamber Recital, April 3, 1990, 2 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 15)
  - Spring Dance Festival, 1970, 1 regular 8mm Positive (Box 15)
  - Duke Collegium Musicum, February 2, 1990, 2 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 15)
  - Duke Student Composers' Concert, April 7, 1987, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 16)
  - Bloom Sisters Recital, February 28, 1988, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 16)
  - Frederic Moses and Jane Hawkins Recital, October 26, 1986, 2 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 16)
  - Sharon Boaz Recital, December 8, 1978, 3 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 16)
  - Women's Glee Club, 1958-1966, 6 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch
    - Vineland Concert, April 3, 1960, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 16)
    - Rochester, NY, March 29, 1960, 3 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 16)
    - Lakeland, FA, March 27, 1966, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 16)
    - Dad's Day Concert, October 30, 1958, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 16)
  - Men's Glee Club, 1958-1967, 5 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch
    - Bethlehem, PA, March 29, 1967, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 16)
    - Hatfield, March 30, 1960, 2 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 16)
    - [Orlando, FL], March 31, 1966, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 16)
    - Winter Concert, February 25, 1958, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 16)
  - [Music 31], undated, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 16)
  - North Carolina Symphony and Woodwind Quintet, May 4, 1974, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 16)
  - University of Illinois Summer Orchestra, August 4, 1960, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 16)
  - North Carolina Chamber Players, November 10, 1978, 2 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 16)
  - Chapel Choir, 1958-1961, 3 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch
    - Dad's Day Concert, October 31, 1958, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 16)
    - Messiah, December 10, 1961, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 16)
    - Messiah, December 4, 1960, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 16)
  - Chancel Singers rehearsal, Spring 1959, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 16)
  - Duke Collegium Musicum, March 4, 1979, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 16)
  - Duke Symphony Orchestra, 1963, 6 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch
    - December 17, 1963 concert with Susan Starr, 4 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 16)
    - March 20, 1963 concert, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 16)
    - May 9, 1963 concert with Helen Boatwright and Robert Nagel, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 16)
  - Duke University Wind Symphony, 1973-1988 (Box 17)
  - Collegium Musicum, 1978-1982, 13 sound reels; 7-inch, 1/4 inch
    - November 13, 1979 concert, 2 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 17)
    - March 30, 1979 concert, 2 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 17)
    - March 25, 1980 concert, 2 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 17)
    - March 30, 1982 concert, 2 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 17)
    - November, 21, 1986 concert, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 17)
    - Lawn Concert, April 22, 1973, 2 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 17)
    - November 29, 1988 concert with Robert Washburn and James Ketch, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 17)
    - November 18, 1975 concert, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 17)
  - John Hanks and Ruth Friedberg, undated, 6 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 17)
  - Collegium Musicum 1978-1984, 9 sound reels; 7-inch, 1/4 inch
    - November 11, 1978 concert, 2 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 17)
    - April 17, 1980 concert, 2 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 17)
    - November 14 and 21, 1982 concerts, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 17)
    - April 17, 1981 concert, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 17)
    - Spanish Music of Love and Death, November 16, 1980, 2 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 17)
    - April 8, 1984 concert, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 17)
  - Student Concerto Concert, April 10, 1979, 2 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 17)
  - Randall Love Piano Recital, October 25, 1988, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 17)
  - Steven Kimbrough and Ruth Friedberg, September 20, 1975, 2 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 17)
  - Duke Symphony Orchestra, 1979, 1988, 2 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch
    - December 12, 1979 concert, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 17)
    - October 8, 1988 concert, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 17)
  - Duke Symphony Orchestra, 1964-1988 and undated, 24 sound reels; 7-inch, 1/4 inch, 1 sound reel; 5-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 18)
    - March 2, 1977 concert, 3 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 18)
    - October 26, 1978 concert, 3 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 18)
    - Undated concert, 2 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 18)
    - October 25, 1988 concert, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 18)
    - December 6, 1988 concert, 2 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 18)
    - February 22, 1979 concert, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 18)
    - February 21, 1975 concert with Murray Perahia, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 18)
    - March 22, 1964, Music for Organ and Strings, 1 sound reel, 5-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 18)
    - Student Concerti, undated, 2 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 18)
    - [St. Petersburg, Florida], March 28, 1966, 2 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 18)
    - [Venice, Florida], April 2, 1966, 3 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 18)
    - [Sarasota, Florida], April 1, 1966, 2 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 18)
    - [Orlando, Florida], March 31, 1966, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 18)
    - [Abingdon, Pennsylvania], March 4, 1965, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 18)
  - Randall Love Piano Recital, October 25, 1988, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 18)
  - Student Compositions, 1986, 2 sound reels, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 18)
  - Juilliard Orchestra, November 9, 1962, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 18)
  - Michael Ching Recital, November 16, 1979, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 18)
  - Michael Ching department studio recording, December 20, 1979, 1 sound reel, 7-inch, 1/4 inch (Box 18)